

Abhishek Pawar

Frontend Developer

Career Objective

To pursue a challenging career and be a part of progressive organization that gives a scope to enhance my knowledge and utilize my skills towards the growth of the organization.

Synopsis

 I possess a total of 2 years of experience in Front End Development, with a significant focus on React.js. Specifically, I have 1 years of dedicated experience in React.js development, complemented by expertise in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, AJAX, jQuery, and Bootstrap.

Professional Experience

Intelliconnect Technologies | Frontend Developer

20/02/2023 - Current

Key responsibilities:

- Develop responsive websites using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, React Js, Next Js.
- Work with REST API's.
- Work with Tech leads on scoping and planning effort estimation and timeline for development.

Plus91 Technologies Pvt Ltd | Frontend Developer

21/03/2022 - 7/11/2022

Key responsibilities:

- Develop responsive websites using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, React Js.
- Work with REST API's.
- Work with Tech leads on scoping and planning effort estimation and timeline for development.

Spwebconnect Solutions | Trainee Software Developer

14th May 2021 - 21st March 2022

Key responsibilities:

- Client: thecooldaddy
- Designed(http://thecooldaddy.com)(responsive pages using html5, css3, JQuery,Js).
- Work with Tech leads on scoping and planning effort estimation and timeline for development.

Gatitaa Technology | Php Intern

31st October 2020 - 25th February 2021

Key responsibilities:

MERN Stack

- ·Client: Saturotechnologies
- Designed(https://saturotech.com/netsuite-erp.php) (responsive pages using html5, css3, JQuery,Js).
- Work with Tech leads on scoping and planning effort estimation and timeline for development.

Certification Course

My Contact

abhishekpwr944@gmail.com

7276343346

Pimple Saudagar,Pune,Maharashtra

www.linkedin.com/in/abhishek-ap7

https://github.com/abhip75/React-dashboard

Primary Skill

- · HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Javascript,
- AJAX, JQuery, React Js, Next Js,
- Redux Js, Node Js,
- Express Js, MongoDB, MySQL,
- React Dev Tool, Redux Dev Tool,
- GIT, Material UI.

Secondary Skill

Tailwind CSS

Education Background

- Master Of Computer Science (MCS)
 Pune University
 Completed in 2020
- Bachelor Of Computer Science (BCS)
 Pune University
 Completed in 2018
- HSC

SSC

Pune Board

Completed in 2013

Pune Board
Completed in 2011